A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Administration, Building Services, Ford Foundation Headquarters, New Building Planning and Construction Files FA500
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Construction Files, 1959-1971, bulk 1963-1969; 1963-1969; III; 12.87 Cubic Feet
  - Reports -- Building Committee -- Monthly Report -- Letters, 1963 June 12-1965 June 18 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Reports -- Building Examined -- 328-334 East 43rd St. -- John V. Dinan, 1964 March 20 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Reports -- Building Examination -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers (1 of 3), 1964 March 20 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Building Examination -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers (2 of 3), 1964 March 20 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Building Examination -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers (3 of 3), 1964 March 20 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Concrete Pours -- Phase I -- R.W. Hunt (1 of 10), 1965 January 25-May 12 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Concrete Pours -- Phase I -- R.W. Hunt (2 of 10), 1965 May 19-August 5 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (3 of 10), 1965 August 19-December 21 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (4 of 10), 1965 December 2-1966 March 24 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (5 of 10), 1966 March 2-May 20 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (6 of 10), 1966 April 27-July 14 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (7 of 10), 1966 June 10-August 31 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (8 of 10), 1966 September 15-November 22 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (9 of 10), 1966 December 12-1967 March 14 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Concrete Test Cylinder -- R.W. Hunt (10 of 10), 1967 March 20-November 30 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (1 of 10), 1964 November 2-1965 March 10 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (2 of 10), 1965 March 11-July 22 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (3 of 10), 1965 July 23-December 31 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (4 of 10), 1966 January 3-May 14 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (5 of 10), 1966 May 16-August 31 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (6 of 10), 1966 September 1-December 30 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (7 of 10), 1967 January 3-May 26 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (8 of 10), 1967 May 27-September 6 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (9 of 10), 1967 September 7-December 29 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Daily Construction (10 of 10), 1968 January 1-December 31 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Excavation Inspection, 1964 August 26 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Final Mechanical Inspection, 1968 March 26 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Final Report on the New Building, 1970 June (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Heat Exchangers -- Certificate of Inspection, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Mechanical Inspection -- Cosentini Associates, 1968 March 28 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Reports -- Re-examination Report with Opinion and Estimate -- 800 Second Avenue -- John V. Dinan [photos separated], 1965 September 20 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Reports -- Re-examination Report with Opinion and Estimate -- 328-334 East 43rd St. Hermitage -- John V. Dinan [photos separated], 1965 September 20 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Reports -- Re-examination Report with Opinion -- Park West and South Walls -- John V. Dinan, 1965 September 30 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud and Associates (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud and Associates (2 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud and Associates (3 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Structural Design Analysis -- Severud and Associates (4 of 4), 1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Transmittal Letters and Field Inspection, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Field Welding (1 of 2), 1965 December 30-1966 September 7 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Field Welding (2 of 2), 1966 September 9-1967 August 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Reports -- Structural Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson -- Shop Welding, 1965 November 5-1966 November 11 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Reports -- Surveying -- Earl B. Lovell-S.P. Belcher Inc., 1965 December 21-1968 July 15 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Reports -- Ultrasonic Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson, 1967 July 24 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Reports -- Sub-surface Investigations, 1964 September 24-25 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (1 of 4), 1964 December 21-28 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (2 of 4), 1965 January 7-February 5 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (3 of 4), 1965 February 15-March 19 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study for Turner Construction Co. (4 of 4), 1965 March 22-May 18 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Reports -- Vibration Study of Blasting -- John V. Dinan Consulting Engineers, 1964 May 11-15 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Resilient Flooring -- Hercules Flooring Co., 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Revolving Doors, Faceplates, Key Stations, etc. -- General Bronze Corp. (1 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Revolving Doors, Faceplates, Key Stations, etc. -- General Bronze Corp. (2 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Rolling Shutters -- The Abbotsford Co. (Crawford Door) -- Contract and Correspondence Re: Bidding, 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Roll-up Doors -- The Kinnear Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Roofing and Flashings -- Tuttle Roofing -- Sketch and Background, 1966 March 7 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Room Finish Schedules, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Rubbish Removal -- P and F Trucking -- Contracts, 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Scaffolding -- Harsco Corp., 1966 May 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Schedules, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Schedules -- Memoranda Re: Completion Schedule, 1967 March 21-July 7 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Sidewalk Bridges -- Richard C. Mugler Co., Inc. -- Contract, Work Authorization, etc., 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Sketches -- Ford Foundation Headquarters -- Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Sketches -- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Skylight -- Fisher Skylight Inc. -- Bidding, Contract, Work Authorization, etc., 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Slate -- Friedman Marble and Slate Works, Inc. -- Approved Sketches, 1967 January 16-30 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Slate -- Friedman Marble and Slate Works, Inc. -- Bidding, Contract, Change Orders, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Snow Melting -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Background Re: Installing Sidewalk Snow Melting Coils, 1965 July 7-1969 January 30 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Sprinkler System -- J.L. Murphy Inc. -- Equipment List, 1965 October 8 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Sprinkler System -- J.L. Murphy Inc. -- Bids, Contract, Work Authorization, etc., 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Steel Inspection -- Gulick-Henderson Testing Labs, 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Strikes -- Plumbers and Derrick Operators -- News Clippings and Memoranda, 1966 August 8-1967 October 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Bolt Orders and Sketches, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Building Enclosure -- Drawings, 1966 December 21 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Camber in Steel Beams, 1966 February 2 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Correspondence Re: Specification Approval, 1965 August 3-1969 June 6 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- KO-674/KO-675 -- Illustrations, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Plans, 1965 October 31 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Structural -- American Bridge Division -- Plans, 1965 November (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Structural Concrete -- C.E. Youngdahl and Co., 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Subcontractors -- C.E. Youngdahl and Co. -- Contract, Correspondence, Change Orders, etc. (1 of 2), 1965-1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Subcontractors -- C.E. Youngdahl and Co. -- Contract, Correspondence, Change Orders, etc. (2 of 2), 1965-1970 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Subcontractors -- General Conditions, 1964 November 27-1965 April 20 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Subcontractors -- List, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Subcontractors -- Port-O-San Corp. -- Correspondence Re: Subcontract, 1964 December 3-1965 August 31 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Subcontractors and Suppliers -- Prospective, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Subcontractors -- Surveying -- Correspondence Re: Contract, 1963 July 19-1965 December 17 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Subcontractors -- Thomas Crimmins -- Contract with Turner Construction Co., 1964 December 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Telephone Equipment Rooms -- Memoranda Re: Phone System, Background, 1963-1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Facilities -- Correspondence, Notes, Order Information, Background, 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Trustee Budget Report -- Cost Analysis of Building Construction, 1970 March 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Correspondence (1 of 3), 1964 October 15-1965 December 9 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Correspondence (2 of 3), 1965 December 2-1967 February 17 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Correspondence (3 of 3), 1967 February 23-December 29 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Meetings -- Reports (1 of 3), 1963-1967 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Meetings -- Delegation, Bids, Miscellaneous Cost Figures (2 of 3), 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Meetings -- New Delhi Building -- Progress Reports (3 of 3), 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Minutes, Notes and Memoranda, 1964 January 20-1965 June 15 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Trustees Building Committee -- Purchase of 328 East 43rd Street, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Minutes, etc., 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Copies of SIS Volume I, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Approval Letters, 1968 April 8-September 20 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Budget Report, 1966-1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (1 of 6), 1965 January 26-November 9 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (2 of 6), 1965 November 23-1966 April 7 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (3 of 6), 1966 April 21-September 23 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (4 of 6), 1966 October 13-1967 February 21 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (5 of 6), 1967 March 9 - July 6 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Construction Job Meetings -- Minutes (6 of 6), 1967 July 20-1968 January 15 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Design -- Minutes (1 of 3), 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Design -- Minutes (2 of 3), 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Building Design -- Minutes (3 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Daily Report and Progress Schedule, 1968 April 27-1969 January 13 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contract (1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contract (2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contractor -- Correspondence Re: Contract Documents (1 of 3), 1963 August 1-1965 September 13 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contractor -- Correspondence Re: Contract Documents (2 of 3), 1965 September 17-1966 July 8 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Management Contractor -- Correspondence Re: Contract Documents (3 of 3), 1966 July 15-1969 August 4 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Punch List -- Meeting Minutes, Memoranda, etc. (1 of 2), 1967 December 18-1968 September 19 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Punch List -- Floor plans (2 of 2), 1967 December 21-1968 January 13 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Schedule of Field Operations -- Construction Schedule (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Schedule of Field Operations -- Construction Schedule (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Sketches (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Turner Construction Co. -- Sketches (2 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Unit Prices -- H.L. Lazar Inc. -- Re: Alteration in New Building, 1967 July 24 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Vertical Conveyor Work -- Lamson Corp., 1965 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Waterproofing and Damp-Proofing -- Munro Waterproofing -- Contract, Bids, etc., 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Window Blinds -- International Building Products, 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Plans and Board of Standards and Appeals Ruling, 1970 September 30-December 30 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear Co. -- Skyclimber -- Requirements, Change Order, Resolution, Correspondence Re: Contract and Government Approval, Maintenance Contract, etc. (1 of 3), 1966-1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear Co. -- Skyclimber -- Correspondence Re: Contract and Government Approval, Background etc. (2 of 3), 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Western Gear Co. -- Skyclimber -- Maintenance Contract, Permit Approvals, Correspondence, etc. (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Wood Flooring -- Klepp Wood Flooring Corp., 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Work Authorizations, 1964-1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Work Drawings and Specifications, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Equipment and Furnishings, 1961-1969; IV; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  Series IV. Equipment and Furnishing, 1961-1969
  The files in this series document the outfitting of the building interior, the purchase of furniture, and the acquisition of moveable equipment. The earliest files contain information about the demonstration of experimental furniture designs by seven different possible vendors intended for the new building (1964-1965), painting estimates (1965), and the disposal of old furniture (1966-1967). Other files pertain to the planning, budgeting, and specifications for the new furniture (1965-1966) and the planning and installation of cable television in the new headquarters building (1966-1969). The files are arranged alphabetically.
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Additional Office Space -- Memoranda and Estimates Re: Experimental Furniture, 1964 November 30-1965 March 12 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Experiments -- 20th Floor Trial Offices -- Notes, Memoranda, Plans, 1963 September 23-1965 March 12 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Painting, Construction and Redecorating Estimates, 1965 February 2-March 12 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Schmid, Robert -- Correspondence Re: Alterations and Refurbishing, 1961 November 2-1963 February 19 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 477 Madison Avenue -- Termination of Lease, Services and Furniture Disposal, 1966 January 26-1967 March 30 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Proposal and Lists (1 of 4), 1966-1969 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Stage Equipment Contract (2 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- Correspondence and Drawings (3 of 4), 1968 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Audiovisual -- Rosner TV -- CATV Installation (4 of 4), 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Carpets -- Lord and Adams -- Quotes for 10th and 11th Floors, 1966 June 15-1967 July 12 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Herman Miller -- Price Quotations, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - File Equipment -- Diebold, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Food Service Equipment -- Heifetz Metal Crafts, Inc., 1968 January 18-March 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Furniture and Equipment Needs -- Central Services -- Lists, 1965 October 18-November 22 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Furniture and Furnishings -- Memoranda Re: Planning, Budgets, Specifications, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Furniture -- Bids, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Furniture -- Decorating -- Metro Decorators, Inc. -- Bills, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Furniture -- Design costs -- Budget and Floor Plans, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Furniture -- Experimental Mock-up -- 477 Madison Avenue 20th Floor -- R.H. McCarthy's File -- Irwin Miller Memorandum, 1963-1965 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Furniture -- Standards -- Estimates, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Furniture -- Specifications, Estimates, Correspondence Re: Purchases, Drawings (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Furniture -- Specifications, Estimates, Correspondence Re: Purchases, Drawings (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Furniture -- Wall Alternative Selections -- Drawings, 1967 January 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Interior Design -- Summary of Commitments and Expenses, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Interior Design -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Furnishing Price Quotes and Specifications, 1965 December 20-1966 September 16 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Irving and Casson -- Trading Desk Plans, Contract, Inventories, 1966-1968 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Lehigh Furniture Corp. -- Correspondence, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - M. Gerber Construction Co. -- Furniture Installation (cabinets, closets, etc.), 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - New Building -- Miscellaneous Desk and Equipment Requirements -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Desks, Telephones, etc., 1967 February-May (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Sketches -- Credenza and Shelving, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Window Washing Equipment -- Skyclimber -- Illustrations, 1966 July 18 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Building Services, 1951-1998, bulk 1964-1969; 1964-1969; V; 3.23 Cubic Feet
  Series V. Building Services, 1951-1998 (bulk 1964-1969)
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, the Building Services series files include correspondence and sub-leases associated with the Foundation's departure from its office space at 477 Madison Avenue (1966-1968). Other files pertain to the outside use of the Foundation's new building facilities and the development of policies (1968-1970). In addition there are inventory sheets that were removed from boxes processed as part of the building plans preservation project of the late 1990s (1971-1998).
  - Accounting System -- Proposed, 1968 February 27 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Allied Handi-Man Company -- Proposal, Analysis, Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Analysis of 7th Floor Area, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Art -- Inventory from 477 Madison Avenue, 1967 February 23-November 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Art Program -- Memoranda and Correspondence Re: Art Purchases, Andrew Ritchie, 1966-1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Budget Control Operations -- Budget Report, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Building Plans Project -- Accession Records -- Blueprints -- Memorandum and Records Transfer Inventories, 1974 August 10-1987 October 7 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Building Plans Project -- Box Inventory Sheets, 1971 January 19 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Building Plans Project -- Box Inventory Sheets of Building Plans -- Old Copies, 1973-1998 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Building Plans Project -- Box Inventory Sheets, 1993-1995 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Building Plans Project -- Building Construction File Index -- Box Inventory Sheets, 1963-1969 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Building Plans Project -- Index of Ford Foundation Building Plans and Drawings [Paradox Database], 1997 July 18 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Building Plans Project -- Meeting Agenda, Blueprint Inventory, 1993 November 17 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Cable TV -- New York Telephone Co. -- Correspondence Re: Hookups, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cash Register -- Proposal, 1966 April 7 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Certificates of Approval -- Re: Electrical, Window Washing, Mail Conveyor, etc., 1968 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Completion -- Claims -- Turner, Mills, etc. -- Correspondence and Memoranda Re: Outstanding Claims, 1967-1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- General, 1966 January 17-1967 November 7 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- General -- Financial Reports, Litigation, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Headquarters -- Miscellaneous, 1967 January 3-1968 January 29 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Re: Rosner TV to Phil Kemp, 1968 April 18-19 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Re: Complaints, Turner Construction, Insurance, etc. (1 of 4), 1964 February-November (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Re: Park Department, Architects, Zoning, etc. (2 of 4), 1964 December-1965 February (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Chronological Correspondence of R.H. McCarthy (3 of 4), 1965 March-1966 January (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Reading File -- Chronological Correspondence of Robert E. Ashley (4 of 4), 1966 February-December (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Critical Path Program -- Planning Handbook, Bar Chart, Method, 1964-1967 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Elevators -- Memorandum Re: Final Installation, 1967 December 5 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Exterminating Services -- Sameth Exterminating Co., Inc. -- Contract, 1965 September 3 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Fire Control Materials, 1975 June 11 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Fire Safety -- Permits, Approvals, Fire Communications System, 1974-1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Food Service -- New Building -- Memorandum, 1966 July 21 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Garage -- Memorandum Re: Parking Allocation, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Garden -- Correspondence Re: Landscaping Award, Invoices, 1968 June 4-1969 September 30 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Index -- Storage Containers Sent by Architects of Shop Drawings by Contractors and Vendors, and Not Plans List, circa 1966-1995 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Inter-Office Memoranda -- Miscellaneous -- Personal Mail, Design Meeting, etc., 1965 December 16-1966 July 8 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Lists of Contractors, Manufacturers, Suppliers, Chronology of the Ford Foundation Headquarters, circa 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Maintenance and Security -- Dominick G. Riley Detective Bureau, 1965-1968 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of Architects and Construction Groups, 1968 June 18 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous -- Memoranda and Quotations Re: Furnishings, etc. (1 of 2), 1965-1967 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous -- Memoranda and Quotations Re: Furnishings, etc. (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Move to New Building -- Move Coordination Committee Agenda, Plans, Related Correspondence, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Occupancy and Move -- Correspondence, Memoranda, Timetable Re: Move, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Outside Use of Facilities -- Requests, Correspondence, Policy Development, 1968-1970 (Box 49, Folder 8)